Hai DING, Certified Scrum Product Owner

Krakow, Poland

hi.haiding@gmail.com | +48 517 277 354



Certified Scrum Product Owner | Finance Analyst | Product Branding and Design

Professional Summary

A versatile professional with experience in finance and management, translation, language education, product branding, entrepreneurship, and client management. Fluent in English, Chinese, and Japanese, I've authored research in finance and management, worked as a legal translator volunteered in technical workshops, and excelled in customer service, managing complex client inquiries. My skills also include creating engaging content that aligns with brand values, effectively connecting with diverse audiences.

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office tools, Adobe software
- Data analytics tools, Power BI, SQL Server
- Product branding, Design and Critical Thinking
- CRM Salesforce, Omni channel, Jira, confluence
- Agile methodologies, scrum
- Communication and organization
- Marketing, business development
- Financial Metrics and Budgeting, API analysis

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Finance Analyst – Funding Operations | *StoneX Financial (Poland)*

Sept 2023 – Present

- Supporting backend operations for processing client transactions
- Facilitating inbound and outbound payments via global banking systems
- Identifying and mitigating risks associated with financial transactions under AML policies and regulations
- Handling problems and red flags, coordinating with cross-functional departments and banks for facilitating transactions

Trading Service Analyst | StoneX Financial (Poland)

June 2023 – Sept 2023

- Handling client enquiries of products as well as investigating and managing trading platforms
- Identifying problems, executing transaction and effectively reporting issues to respective support solutions
- Handling client queries and providing customer support via email, live chats, and calls

Product Branding Manager | Panglossian Studios (China)

Sept 2022 – Jan 2023

- Defining project's objectives, conducting market research on business and client development
- Creating and publishing visual and reading contents that fit brand image
- Providing product branding, photography, videography, and graphic design with cultural characteristics
- Analyzing, developing and implementing strategies to achieve company goals

Business Law Translator | CBL - Chinese Business Law - Translation (China)

Nov 2020 – June 2022

- Managing service agreements and literature essays for corporate business
- Chinese-English translation of legal contracts and patents

Freelancing Sept 2018 – June 2022

- Sales executive for China import and export fair
- Japanese Interpreter for One-Belt One-Road international medical conference
- Customer technical support for Genshin Impact game, Mihoyo
- Legal contract translator and consultant for Grandall Law firm
- Content writer for promoting and advertising products and organizations on social media
- Freelance English teacher

EDUCATION

MBA | Masters of Business and Finance Management | Jagiellonian University

July 2024

Bsc | Bachelor of English and English Literature | Weifang Medical University

June 2022

AWARDS

- 2nd Place prize in Shandong University Debating Championship (2019)
- 2nd Place prize of public speech on Foreign Language Teaching and Research Press FLTRP (2018)
- Award in technical creative innovation, Jilin (2015)

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Founder and director of English language training center, China
- Leader of business and entrepreneurship student organization, Weifang Medical University, China
- Volunteer of technical workshop and cross-cultural community projects
- Author of research paper in finance, management and market analysis

LANGUAGES

Chinese (Native)

English (Fluent)

Japanese (Fluent)

French (B2)

HOBBIES

- Writing music and singing
- Badminton
- Learning languages